Paper (Ken-Jung) Lee

paper.li@gmail.com
https://paperworkstud.io

Brief

PRODUCT DESIGN | PROTOTYPING | AR/VR

Paper Lee is a Taiwanese-origin product designer with more than a decade of digital product experience. He has been participating in designing products across spatial computing, AR/VR, IOT mobile apps, and TV voice gaming platforms. He has expertise in product design, prototyping, and interaction design.

Experience

LEAD PRODUCT DESIGNER VOLLEY, SAN FRANCISCO, AUG. 2023 - NOW

PRODUCT DESIGNER

VOLLEY, SAN FRANCISCO, MAR. 2022 - JUL. 2023

UI and UX design for voice games and applications in smart speakers and smart TVs, i.e., Echo Show devices, FireTV, Roku, etc. Wireframes, voice and visual flows, prototyping, and high-fidelity visual designs.

LEAD PRODUCT DESIGNER

DIING, TAIPEI / LOS ANGELES, JUN. 2016 - FEB. 2022

In-house design team leading, full-stack product design for VR and IOT mobile app services. Company branding and websites design and development.

SENIOR PRODUCT DESIGNER

UNIGREEN, TAIPEI, AUG. 2015 - MAY 2016

In-house design team leading, full-stack product design for agriculture goods shopping experiences.

SENIOR USER INTERFACE DESIGNER

MOBIAPPS, TAIPEI, DEC. 2012 - JUL. 2015

Full-stack product design for company websites, e-commerce, and OEM mobile services.

USER INTERACTION DESIGNER

PILOTFISH, MUNICH, AUG. 2011 - AUG. 2012

Design research, brainstorming, ideation, user interface design, graphic design, and prototyping.

USABILITY ENGINEER

KATDC, TAIPEI, SEP. 2008 - JUN. 2011

In-house Usability lab build-up, prototyping, and usability assessments for TV software products

MECHANICAL ENGINEER

CTCI, TAIPEI, MAR. 2008 - AUG. 2008

Design the static equipment for chemical planets.

Education

M.S., BIOMEDICAL ENGINEERING

NATIONAL YANG-MING UNIVERSITY, TAIPEI, 2005 - 2007

"3D Dynamic Model Construction for Predicting Knee Kinematics - Comparison of native knee and knee arthroplasty", presented on the 21th Congress of International Society of Biomechanics

"Three-dimensional Dynamic Model Construction for Predicting Knee Kinematics - Comparison of Native Knee and Knee Arthroplasty", Masters thesis

B.S., MECHANICAL AND ELECTRO-MECHANICAL ENGINEERING NATIONAL SUN YAT-SEN UNIVERSITY, KAOHSIUNG, 2001 - 2005

"Man back-supporting system - A best supporting points analysis", presented on the 21th National Conference on Mechanical Engineering of CSME

Skills

Tool

Sketch, Framer, Affinity Photo/Designer/Publisher, Blender, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Adobe After Effects, Lottie Animation, InVision, Marvel

HTML/CSS/JavaScript, Jekyll, React, Swift, iOS development, Android development

Unity, Xcode, Android Studio, Lens Studio, Spark AR Studio, Oculus, SteamVR, Marquette

User Experience Design

Prototyping, mobile app design, web design, UI design, UX design, AR design, VR design, interaction design, visual design, User-Centered Design

Language

English, Mandarine

Portfolio

paperworkStudio

https://paperworkstud.io

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/paperli/